Faculty of Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Faculty of Science fonds
1965 - 2000
F-24
8.26 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
DATES OF CREATION The predominant dates for records in this fonds are 1965-1996. Five files contain publications and annual reports that date 1997-2000.
Financial assistance for the arrangement and description of the records and production of the finding aid was generously provided by the Dean of the Faculty of Science in 2006.
Faculty of Science
The Faculty of Science is one of the three founding faculties of Simon Fraser University. The Faculty was established in September 1965, as mandated by the Universities Act, 1963. c.52 (RS 1979, c. 419). The four charter departments of the Faculty consisted of Biological Sciences, Chemistry, Mathematics and Statistics, and Physics. As of 2006, the Faculty has grown to eight departments and also includes Earth Sciences, Environmental Sciences, Molecular Biology and Biochemistry, and Statistics and Actuarial Science (the only program of its kind in western North America.)
The Dean of Science reports to the Vice-President Academic and Provost. Each department in the Faculty is headed by a Chair and the Dean is assisted by an Associate Dean. The Dean is both the chief officer and chair of faculty meetings and is responsible for ensuring that the various duties and responsibilities of the Faculty are carried out.
Each of the departments offers BSc, MSc, and PhD degrees and participates in the university's co-operative education program that allows students to combine relevant work experience with academic studies. The Faculty of Science also offers several courses that can be used by non-science students to fulfill degree requirements. In 2005 the Faculty began offering science programs at SFU's Surrey campus.
The Faculty of Science is a research-intensive faculty, traditionally accounting for half the external research support (and funding) brought to SFU. The Faculty has actively supported a high school recruitment policy through high school liaison programs established in the late 1960's and more recently, hiring a Director of Student recruitment. The Faculty of Science also plays a role in university outreach by promoting a general understanding of scientific discoveries and explaining the implications of science for setting social policy. Through the School for Continuing Studies, the faculty sponsors science seminar series that are held in the evenings at Harbour Centre. Graduate and undergraduate students from the faculty annually run summer science camps and maintain the “Science Alive!” and “Let's talk Science” programs.
SFU is one of five universities involved in research at TRIUMF, Canada's National Laboratory for Particle and Nuclear Physics located at the University of British Columbia. In addition, SFU is one of five universities that form the Western Canadian Universities Marine Biological Society (WCUMBS), a non-profit group that owns and operates the Bamfield Marine Sciences Centre, in Bamfield, BC.
published
Full
Revised
The title of the fonds is based on the name of the creating body.
The fonds consists of records relating to the academic development of the Faculty of Science and the departmental administration of Biological Sciences, Chemistry, Mathematics and Physics. Activities, topics and events documented include the Dean's correspondence with faculty and departmental chairs; correspondence with the university community, local and international science professionals, and provincial and national organizations; departmental reviews; participation on university committees and the Management Council of the Western Canadian Universities Marine Biological Society; liaison with university research institutes; and construction of the South Science Building on campus.
The types of documents include meeting agendas, minutes, and supporting papers; correspondence and reports; annual reports; budgets and financial working papers; speeches; policies and procedures; bound architectural drawings; and publications including newsletters, pamphlets, journals, conference programs, posters, research summaries, and a calendar.
The titles and arrangement of series were provided by the archivist. During the processing of accruals in 2006 the archivist attempted to add records to existing series by creating sub-series. Series 2 "Faculty Research Information" is a closed series. Where possible new files have been arranged chronologically without disturbing original file classfication numbers.
Nelson, C. Donald; Rieckhoff, Klaus E.; Funt, B. Lionel; Srivastava, Lalit M.; Barlow, John S.; Aronoff, Sam; Webster, John M.; Cochrane, John F.; Geen, Glen H.; Jones, Colin H. W.; Irwin, J. Chuck; Davidson, W. S.; Mathewes, Rolf; Plischke, Michael; Tuck, D. G.
The records were transferred to Archives through the regular application of university Records Retention Schedules and Disposal Authorities (RRSDAs).
All accessions have been processed as of July 2006. Further accruals are expected.
For related records please see the Department of Biological Sciences fonds (F-5), the Department of Chemistry fonds (F-6), the Department of Mathematics fonds (F-14), the Department of Physics fonds (F-19), the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies fonds (F-21), the Office of the President fonds (F-193), the Office of the Vice-President Academic and Provost fonds (F-200), and the Academic Planning Services fonds (F-202).
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
A file list is available for these records.
- Dean's administrative records and correspondence, 1965 - 2000; F-24-1; 5.04 m of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the administration of the Faculty of Science and includes minutes from the Faculty of Science meetings and Faculty of Science Chairmen's meetings; the Dean's correspondence with faculty departments, the B.C. Science Council, the University Research Park, TRIUMF, the University College of the Fraser Valley, the Eastern Islands University Development Project, and the Western Canadian Universities Marine Biology Society. It also contains correspondence with research institutes including the Theoretical Science Institute, the Institute for Energy, the Institute for Aquaculture Research, the Applied Mathematics Institute, and the Environmental Science Research Institute. Also included are departmental reviews and annual reports; the development of faculty policies, procedures, and curriculum guidelines; NSERC grant proposals and National Research Council awards and applications; and records on the construction of campus buildings including the South Science Building and drawings for the Science Complex.
  Records include correspondence, working papers, reports, meeting agendas and minutes, grant applications, and bound architectural drawings.
  British Columbia Science Council; University College of the Fraser Valley; Eastern Islands University Development project; Applied Mathematics Institute; Environmental Science Research Institute; National Research Council; Natural Science and Engineering Research Council; Department of Biological Sciences; Department of Chemistry
  For further material relating to the Albert Einstein Centennial Lectures series found in F-24-1-5-0-47, see (F-182) The Evelyn T. and Leigh Hunt Palmer Science Collection.
  - Chronological correspondence, 1968 - 1979; F-24-1-1; 1 m of textual records
    The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
    Further accruals to the sub-series are expected.
    Access to files containing personal information of third parties or confidential business information of third-party organizations may be restricted. Please see the file list and consult with the archivist for more details.
    A file list is available.
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1968; F-24-1-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1969; F-24-1-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1970; F-24-1-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1971; F-24-1-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1972; F-24-1-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1973; F-24-1-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 24-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1974; F-24-1-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 24-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1975; F-24-1-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1976; F-24-1-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 24-6)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 7, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 8, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 9, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 10, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 11, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 12, 1977; F-24-1-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 2, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 3, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 24-7)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 4, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 5, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 6, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 7, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 8, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 9, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 10, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 11, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 12, 1978; F-24-1-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
    - Chronological correspondence, vol. 1, 1979; F-24-1-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 24-8)
  - Memoranda and notices, 1968 - 1979; F-24-1-2; 16 cm of textual records
    - Memoranda and notices, 1968; F-24-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-1-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-1-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-1-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-1-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1974; F-24-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1974; F-24-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 1, 1975; F-24-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-9)
    - Memoranda and notices, vol. 2, 1975; F-24-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Memoranda and notices, 1976; F-24-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Memoranda and notices, 1977 - 1979; F-24-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Memoranda - Chairs, 1971 - 1973; F-24-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
  - Departmental reviews, 1968 - 1977; F-24-1-3; 21 cm of textual records
    Some records contain personal information relating to "Departmental reviews". Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Departmental reviews, 1969 - 1973; F-24-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Biological Sciences, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Biological Sciences, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Biological Sciences, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Biological Sciences, vol. 4, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Chemistry, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Chemistry, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Chemistry, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Chemistry, 1972 - 1973; F-24-1-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-10)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 4, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 5, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, 1972 - 1973; F-24-1-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 1, 1972 - 1977; F-24-1-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Mathematics, vol. 2, 1972 - 1977; F-24-1-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Physics, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Physics, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-1-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Departmental reviews - Physics, 1972 - 1973; F-24-1-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
    - Physics appointments, 1968; F-24-1-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-11)
  - Faculty of Science annual reports, 1980 - 2000; F-24-1-4; 24 cm of textual records
    - Annual Report No. 1, 1980 - 1981; F-24-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
      Open
    - Annual Report No. 2, 1981 - 1982; F-24-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
    - Annual Report No. 3, 1982 - 1983; F-24-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
    - Annual Report No. 4, 1983 - 1984; F-24-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
    - Annual Report No. 5, 1984 - 1985; F-24-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
    - Annual Report No. 6, 1985 - 1986; F-24-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-12)
    - Annual Report No. 7, 1986 - 1987; F-24-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Annual Report No. 8, 1987 - 1988; F-24-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Annual Report No. 9, 1988 - 1989; F-24-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Annual Report No. 10, 1989 - 1990; F-24-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 13, 1992 - 1993; F-24-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 14, 1994 - 1995; F-24-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 15, 1995 - 1996; F-24-1-4-0-13 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 16, 1996 - 1997; F-24-1-4-0-14 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 17, 1997 - 1998; F-24-1-4-0-15 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 18, 1998 - 1999; F-24-1-4-0-16 (Archival box - small 24-55)
    - Annual Report No. 19, 1999 - 2000; F-24-1-4-0-17 (Archival box - small 24-55)
  - Faculty of Science administrative records, 1966 - 1998; F-24-1-5; 1.24 m of textual records
    Some records contain personal information relating to "Office files". Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Course enrollments, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Grades and appeals, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Graduate requirements, 1975; F-24-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Graduate calendar, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - Graduate Associates, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-13)
    - New Graduate courses, 1972 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Miscellaneous - transfer credits, 1972 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Pre-registrations, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Regulations and procedures, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Science 010, 1971 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Science Fair, 1973; F-24-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Science workshops, 1971 - 1972; F-24-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Space allocation, 1967 - 1974; F-24-1-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Speeches, lectures, 1972; F-24-1-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - Summer Research Scholarship Program, 1973 - 1975; F-24-1-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-14)
    - NSERC grants, 1980; F-24-1-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - Defense Research Board - misc. correspondence, 1970 - 1974; F-24-1-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-15)
    - Defense Research Board - misc. correspondence, 1970 - 1974; F-24-1-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-15)